Sudhanshu

Energetic software developer with **10 years** of experience developing applications from scratch and maintenance both. Has developed several mobile apps. **4 Years** of experience in leading a team and owning features and product requirements.

Gurugram +91-9958163123 anshusrivastava45@gmail.com

EXPERIENCE

Times Internet Ltd., Gurugram — Sr. iOS Developer

March, 2015 - PRESENT

- Leading Mobile team
- Conducting annual appraisal meetings, Hiring and on-boarding new joiner
- Product requirement discussions
- Leading complete features and revamping of projects
- Sprint planning and Project Estimation.
- Code quality and review.

Techlites Solutions Pvt. Ltd., Delhi — Sr. iOS Developer

March 2014 - March 2015

- Application development, maintenance and testing.
- Sprint planning and project estimation.

Xicom Technologies Ltd., Delhi — *iOS Developer*

Feb 2011 - March 2014

- Application development, maintenance and testing
- Contributed in hiring mobile developers and building new teams.

EDUCATION

Kurukshetra University, Kurukshetra — B. Tech(C.S.E.)

2005 - 2009

Percentage scored: 69.9%

Rao Lal Singh Public School, Gurugram — Intermediate

2004 - 2005

Percentage scored: 76.7%

Jain Public Sr. Sec. School, Dharuhera — *Matriculation*

2002 - 2003

Percentage scored: 81.8%

SOCIAL PRESENCE

Medium GitHub Stack

SKILLS

Swift, Objective-C, Core data, Xcode, React-Native, Android Studio

LANGUAGES

Hindi, English

STRENGTHS

- Quick learner & interested to work in new challenging fields.
- Having good planning and problem solving skills.
- Motivated and dedicated to getting the job done at the right time.

PERSONAL

Father: Sh. Harish Chandra

Mother: Mrs. Kiran Devi

DOB: 11/11/1987

Gender: Male

Marital Status: Married

Nationality: Indian

PROJECTS

Longwalks Times Internet Ltd.

iTunes URL:

https://itunes.apple.com/us/app/longwalks-conversation-app/id1412531085

Times Internet Ltd.

Team Size: 3-4

Longwalks app is a different type of Social Media platform which provides a guided conversation tool in a closed network. It has a fill-in-the-blanks which sparks personal reflection and self-expression, so users can share meaningful and create more intimate relationships.

MensXP Times Internet Ltd.

iTunes URL: https://itunes.apple.com/in/app/id1253494246?mt=8

Team Size: 3

MensXP is India's largest lifestyle community for men. More than 15 million users in India use mensxp.com to get tips and advice on relationships, fashion, fitness, health, grooming, technology, culture, mean machines, women, sports career, LGBT and entertainment in the context of a modern Indian man. The modern Indian man today is neither a sex-obsessed predator nor the stoic automatons our culture so often makes us out to be. We strive to be good fathers and husbands, citizens and friends, to lead by example at home and in the workplace, and to understand their role in a changing world. MensXP helps the modern Indian man discover this.

iDiva Times Internet Ltd.

iTunes URL: https://itunes.apple.com/us/app/id1359022878?ls=1&mt=8

Team Size: 2

iDiva is a community for women where they can find beauty, fashion, wedding, lifestyle tips. The app also serves of original videos from iDiva actors and anchors.

Indiatimes Times Internet Ltd.

iTunes URL: https://itunes.apple.com/in/app/id717209912?mt=8

Team Size: 3

Indiatimes app brings you the latest news and trending stories from India and around the world. Get stories that matter to our generation. Stay up to date with all that's hot and trending with the all new Indiatimes app.

We're bringing you our take on trending stories, current news and all the buzz from the world of entertainment, lifestyle, technology, sports, health and more

The above statements are true to the best of my knowledge and belief.

Date:/...... Sudhanshu